<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song><head><songTitle>All Bout U</songTitle>
<singer>2Pac</singer>
<featuredsingers>Dru Down, Outlawz, Nate Dogg and 1 mor</featuredsingers>e
<producers>Johnny J and 2Pac</producers>
<album>All Eyez on Me</album>
<certification>Diamond</certification></head>

<lyrics><intro>[<singer>2Pac</singer> + <featuredsinger>Dru Down</featuredsinger>]
Ah, yeah! Hahaha (Yeah!)
It's all about you, one time!
(I'ma say it's all about you, baby, yeah!)
Haha, for the <phrase type="profanity">bitches</phrase> that think it's all about you
It's all about you! (This Dru Down in the house
With my boy 'Pizznac, you know what I'm sayin'?)
It's all about you
(Yeah, I'm gon' say it's all about you
But you know I'm lyin' though, hah! Yeah)</intro>

<verse><singer>[2Pac]</singer>
You probably crooked as the last trick
Want to laugh about how I got my <phrase type="profanity">ass</phrase> caught up
With this bad <phrase type="profanity">bitch</phrase>?
Thinkin' I had her, but she had me in the long run
It's just my luck, I'm stuck with <phrase type="profanity">fuckin'</phrase> with the wrong one
Wise decisions, based on lies we livin'
Scandalous times, this game's like my religion
You could be rollin' with a thug
Instead you with this weak scrub, lookin' for some love
In every club, I see you starin' like you want it
Well, baby, if you got it, better flaunt it
Let the liquor help you get up on it
I'm still tipsy from last night
Bumpin' these walls as I pause, addicted to the fast life
I try to holla, but you tell me you taken
Sayin' you ain't impressed with the money I'm makin'
Guess it's true what they tellin' me
Fresh out of jail, life's <phrase type="profanity">hell</phrase> for a black celebrity
So that's the reason why I call, and maybe you with it
Fantasies of us sweatin', can I hit it?
Addicted to the things you do
But still true what I'm sayin', boo, ‘cause this is all about you</verse>

<chorus>[<featuredsinger>Nate Dogg</featuredsinger> + <singer>2Pac</singer>]
Every other city we go, every other video
It's all about you
No matter where I go, I see the same <phrase type="dt">hoe</phrase>
Yeah, <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>
Every other city we go, every other video
It's all about you
No matter where I go, I see the same <phrase type="dt">hoe</phrase></chorus>

<verse><singer>[2Pac]</singer>
I make a promise if you go with me, just let me know
I'll have you hollerin' my name out before I leave
Nobody loves me, I'm a thug <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>
I only hung out with the criminals and drug dealers
I love <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase>, ‘cause we comin' from the same place
Witness me holla at a hoochie
See how quick the game takes
How can I tell her I'm a playa? And I don't even care
Creep low, weed smoke's in the air
Everywhere I go, it's all about the groupie <phrase type="dt">hoes</phrase>
Waitin' for <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> at the end of every show
I just seen you in my friend's video
Could never put a <phrase type="profanity">bitch</phrase> before my friends, so here we go
Follow the leader and peep the drama that I'm goin' through
It's all about you, yeah, <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>, it's all about you</verse>

<chorus>[<featuredSinger>Nate Dogg</featuredSinger> + <singer>2Pac</singer>]
Every other city we go, every other video
It's all about you
No matter where I go, I see the same <phrase type="dt">hoe</phrase>
Every other city we go, every other video
It's all about you
No matter where I go, I see the same <phrase type="dt">hoe</phrase></chorus>

<verse><featuredSinger>[Hussein Fatal]</featuredSinger>
Is you sick from the dick, or is it the flu?
It ain't about you or your <phrase type="profanity">bitch-ass</phrase> crew
Every other city we go and every video
Explain to a <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase> why I see the same <phrase type="profanity">shitty</phrase> <phrase type="dt">hoe</phrase>
You think it's all about you? Well, boo
I gets down like Dru, and my nasty new <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase>, too</verse>

<chorus><featuredSinger>[Yaki Kadafi]</featuredSinger>
You couldn't hold me back, it'd take a fatter track
A lyrical attack, perhaps, it was a visual bluff
When I started to snaps all your rode 'em swoll
Straight in control, flows'll fold, while <phrase type="dt">hoes</phrase> cold stroll
Hold the set, I told Dramacy' go in next
Gold diggin', cold diggin' a gold Rolex</chorus>
<featuredSinger>
[Hussein Fatal]</featuredSinger>
I slide in easily, try a grizzly
<phrase type="dt">Sluts</phrase> know the cuts, I came to <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase>, try skeezin' me
Runnin' up in ya just like Bruce Jenner when I bend ya
At the most, I <phrase type="profanity">fucked</phrase> a <phrase type="profanity">bitch</phrase>
From the West Coast to West Virginia

<chorus>[<featuredSinger>Nate Dogg</featuredSinger> and <singer>2Pac</singer>]
Every other city we go, every other video
It's all about you
No matter where I go, I see the same <phrase type="dt">hoe</phrase>
Every other city we go, every other video
It's all about you
No matter where I go, I see the same <phrase type="dt">hoe</phrase>
Every other city we go, every other video
It's all about you
No matter where I go, I see the same <phrase type="dt">hoe</phrase>
Every other city we go, every other video
No matter where I go, I see the same <phrase type="dt">hoe</phrase>
</chorus>
<outro>[<featuredSinger>Snoop Doggy Dogg</featuredSinger>]
I'm tellin' ya, it's the same old <phrase type="profanity">shit</phrase>
 I mean, <phrase type="profanity">goddamn</phrase>, you know what I'm sayin'?
<phrase type="lifeEvent">I'm sittin' back, watchin' Montell Jordan video</phrase>
I see the same <phrase type="profanity">bitch</phrase> who was in my homeboy Nate Dogg video, then I flip the channel
<phrase type="lifeEvent">I'm checkin' out my homeboy 2Pac video</phrase>
I see the same <phrase type="profanity">bitch</phrase> that was in my video, you knahmsayin'?
And then, you nahmsayin', what make that even mo' <phrase type="profanity">fucked</phrase> up, I'm watchin' a Million Man March
And I see the same <phrase type="profanity">bitch</phrase>, on the Million Man March
That was in the homeboy Warren G video
I mean, <phrase type="profanity">damn</phrase>, everywhere I look
Everywhere I go, I see the same <phrase type="dt">hoe</phrase>
Don't get mad, I'm only bein' real, yeah</outro></lyrics></song>



