<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song><head><songTitle>How Do U Want It</songTitle>
<singer>2Pac</singer>
<featuredSingers>K-Ci and JoJo</featuredSingers>
<producers>Dalvin DeGrate, 2Pac and Johnny J</producers>
<album>All Eyez on Me</album>
<certification>Diamond</certification></head>

<lyrics><chorus><featuredSingers>[K-Ci and JoJo]</featuredSingers>
How do you want it?
How do you feel?
Comin' up as a <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase> in the cash game
Livin' in the fast lane, I'm for real
How do you want it yeah?
How do you feel?
Comin' up as a <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase> in the cash game
Livin' in the fast lane, I'm for real</chorus>

<verse><singer>[2Pac]</singer>
I love the way you activate your hips and push your <phrase type="profanity">ass</phrase> out
Got a <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase> wantin' it so bad, I'm about to pass out
Wanna dig you, and I can't even lie about it
Baby, just alleviate your clothes, time to fly up out it
Catch you at a club, oh <phrase type="profanity">shit</phrase>, you got me fiendin'
Body talkin' <phrase type="profanity">shit</phrase> to me, but I can't comprehend the meanin'
Now, if you wanna roll with me, then here's your chance
Doin' eighty on the freeway, police, catch me if you can
Forgive me, I'm a rider, still I'm just a simple man
All I want is money, <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase> the fame, I'm a simple man
Mr. International, player with the passport
Just like Aladdin, <phrase type="profanity">bitch</phrase>, get you anything you ask for
It's either him or me; Champagne, Hennessy
A favorite of my homies when we floss on our enemies
Witness as we creep to a low speed, peep what a <phrase type="dt">hoe</phrase> need
Puff some mo' weed, funk, ya don't need
Approachin' hoochies with a passion, been a long day
But I've been driven by attraction in a strong way
Your body is bangin', baby, I love it when you flaunt it
Time to give it to daddy, <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>, now tell me how you want it</verse>

<chorus><featuredSingers>[K-Ci and JoJo]</featuredSingers>
How do you want it?
How does it feel?
Comin' up as a <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase> in the cash game
Livin' in the fast lane, I'm for real
How do you want it?
How do you feel?
Comin' up as a <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase> in the cash game
Livin' in the fast lane, I'm for real</chorus>

<singer>[2Pac]</singer>
Tell me is it cool to <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase>?
Did you think I come to talk? Am I a fool or what?
Positions on the floor, it's like erotic
Ironic, 'cause I'm somewhat psychotic
I'm hittin' switches on <phrase type="profanity">bitches</phrase>
Like I been fixed with hydraulics
Up and down like a roller coaster
I'm up inside ya, I ain't quittin' 'til the show is over
'Cause I'm a rider, in and out just like a robbery
I'll probably be a <phrase type="dt">freak</phrase> and let you get on top of me
Get her rockin' these, nights full of Alize
A livin' legend you ain't heard about
These <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> play these Cali days
C. Delores Tucker, you's a <phrase type="profanity">motherfucker</phrase>
Instead of tryin' to help a <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>, you destroy a brother
Worse than the others; Bill Clinton, Mister Bob Dole
You're too old to understand the way the game's told
You're lame so I gotta hit you with the hot facts
Once I'm released, I'm makin' millions, <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>, top that
They wanna censor me; they'd rather see me in a cell
Livin' in hell, only a few of us'll live to tell
Now everybody talkin' about us, I could give a <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase>
I'd be the first one to bomb and cuss
<phrase type="profanity">Nigga</phrase>, tell me how you want it

[Chorus: K-Ci and JoJo]
How do you want it?
How do you feel?
Comin' up as a <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase> in the cash game
Livin' in the fast lane, I'm for real
How do you want it?
How do you feel?
Comin' up as a <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase> in the cash game
Livin' in the fast lane, I'm for real

<phrase type="profanity">[2Pac]</phrase>
Raised as a youth, tell the truth
I got the scoop on how to get a bulletproof
Because I jumped from the roof before I was a teenager
Mobile phone, Skypager, game rules, I'm livin' major
My adversaries is lookin' worried
They paranoid of gettin' buried
One of us gon' see the cemetery
My only hope to survive if I wish to stay alive
Gettin' high, see the demons in my eyes, before I die
I wanna live my life and ball, make a couple million
And then I'm chillin', fade 'em all
These taxes got me crossed up and people tryin' to sue me
Media is in my business and they actin' like they know me
But I'ma mash out and peel out
I’m with a clique that’s quick to whip that <phrase type="profanity">fuckin'</phrase> steel out
Yeah <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>, it's some new <phrase type="profanity">shit</phrase> so better get up on it
When you see me, tell a <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase> how you want it
How do you want it?

<featuredSinger>[K-Ci and JoJo]</featuredSinger>
How do you want it?
How do you feel?
Comin' up as a <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase> in the cash game
Livin' in the fast lane, I'm for real
How do you want it?
How do you feel?
Comin' up as a <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase> in the cash game
Livin' in the fast lane, I'm for real
How do you want it?
How do you feel?
Comin' up as a <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase> in the cash game
Livin' in the fast lane, I'm for real
How do you want it?
How do you feel?
Comin' up as a <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase> in the cash game
Livin' in the fast lane, I'm for real

<outro><singer>[2Pac]</singer>
Me and my <phrase type="profanity">Nigga</phrase> Johnny J...yeah we out</outro></lyrics></song>

