<song><head><songTitle><line>97' Bonnie and Clyde / Just the Two of Us</line></songTitle>
<artist><line>Eminem</line></artist>
<producer><line>Eminem and Bass Brothers</line></producer>
<album><line>Slim Shady EP</line></album>
<certification><line>Diamond</line></certification></head>

<lyrics><intro>
<line>Baby, your dada loves you</line>
<line>And I'ma always be here for you no matter what happens</line>
<line>You're all I got in this world</line>
<line>I would never give you up for nothin'</line>
<line>Nobody in this world is ever gonna keep you from me</line>
<line>I love you</line></intro>

<chorus><line>C'mon Hai-Hai, we goin' to the beach</line>
<line>Grab a couple of toys and let Dada strap you in the car seat</line>
<line>Oh, where's Mama? She's takin' a little nap in the trunk</line>
<line>Oh, that smell? Dada must've runned over a skunk</line>
<line>Now, I know what you're thinkin', it's kind of late to go swimmin'</line>
<line>But you know your Mama, she's one of those type of women</line>
<line>That do crazy things, and if she don't get her way she'll throw a fit</line>
<line>Don't play with Dada's toy knife, honey, let go of it! (no!)</line>
<line>And don't look so upset, why you actin' bashful?</line>
<line>Don't you wanna help Dada build a sandcastle? (yeah!)</line>
<line>And Mama said she wants to show how far she can float</line>
<line>And don't worry about that little boo-boo on her throat</line>
<line>It's just a little scratch – it don't hurt</line>
<line>Her was eatin' dinner while you were sweepin'</line>
<line>And spilled ketchup on her shirt</line>
<line>Mama's messy, ain't she? We'll let her wash off in the water</line>
<line>And me and you can pway by ourselves, can't we?</line></chorus>

<chorus><line>Just the two of us, just the two of us</line>
<line>And when we ride</line>
<line>Just the two of us, just the two of us</line>
<line>Just you and I</line>
<line>Just the two of us, just the two of us</line>
<line>And when we ride</line>
<line>Just the two of us, just the two of us</line>
<line>Just you and I</line></chorus>

<verse><line>See, honey, there's a place called Heaven and a place called Hell</line>
<line>A place called prison and a place called jail</line>
<line>And Dada's probably on his way to all of 'em except one</line>
<line>‘Cause Mama's got a new husband and a stepson</line>
<line>And you don't want a brother, do ya?</line>
<line>Maybe when you're old enough</line>
<line>To understand a little better, I'll explain it to ya</line>
<line>But for now, we'll just say Mama was real, real bad</line>
<line>She was bein' mean to Dad and made him real, real <phrase type="emotion">mad</phrase></line>
<line>But I still feel <phrase type="emotion">sad</phrase> that I put her on timeout</line>
<line>Sit back in your chair, honey, quit tryna climb out!</line>
<line>I told you it's okay, Hai-Hai, want a ba-ba?</line>
<line>Take a night-night? Nan-a-boo, goo-goo ga-ga?</line>
<line>Her make poo-poo ca-ca? Dada change your didee</line>
<line>Clean the baby up so her can take a nighty-nighty</line>
<line>Your dad'll wake her up as soon as we get to the water</line>
<line>'97 Bonnie and Clyde: me and my daughter</line></verse>

<chorus><line>Just the two of us, just the two of us</line>
<line>And when we ride</line>
<line>Just the two of us, just the two of us</line>
<line>Just you and I</line>
<line>Just the two of us, just the two of us</line>
<line>And when we ride</line>
<line>Just the two of us, just the two of us</line>
<line>Just you and I</line></chorus>

<verse><line>Wake up, sweepyhead, we're here, before we pway</line>
<line>We're gonna take Mama for a wittle walk along the pier</line>
<line>Baby, don't cry, honey, don't get the wrong idea</line>
<line>Mama's too sweepy to hear you screamin' in her ear (Mama!)</line>
<line>That's why you can't get her to wake, but don't worry</line>
<line>Dada made a nice bed for Mommy at the bottom of the lake</line>
<line>Here, you wanna help Dada tie a rope around this rock? (yea)</line>
<line>We'll tie it to her footsie then we'll roll her off the dock</line>
<line>Ready now, here we go, on the count of free</line>
<line>One, two, free — whee! (woosh!)</line>
<line>There goes Mama, spashin' in the water</line>
<line>No more fightin' with Dad, no more restrainin' order</line>
<line>No more stepdada, no more new brother</line>
<line>Blow her kisses bye-bye, tell Mama you wuv her (Mommy!)</line>
<line>Now we'll go play in the sand, build a castle and junk</line>
<line>But first, just help Dad with two more things out the trunk</line></verse>

<chorus><line>Just the two of us, just the two of us</line>
<line>And when we ride</line>
<line>Just the two of us, just the two of us</line>
<line>Just you and I</line>
<line>Just the two of us, just the two of us</line>
<line>And when we ride</line>
<line>Just the two of us, just the two of us</line>
<line>Just you and I</line></chorus>

<outro><line>Just me and you, baby, is all we need in this world</line>
<line>Just me and you</line>
<line>Your dada will always be there for you</line>
<line>Your dada's always gonna love you, remember that</line>
<line>If you ever need me I will always be here for you</line>
<line>If you ever need anything, just ask</line>
<line>Dada will be right there</line>
<line>Your dada loves you — I love you, baby</line></outro></lyrics>



</song>