<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../rapSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <head>
        <songTitle>As the World Turns</songTitle>
        <artist>Eminem</artist>
        <producer>Eminem</producer>
        <producer>Bass Brothers</producer>
        <album>The Slim Shady LP</album>
        <certification>Diamond</certification>
        <order>39</order>
    </head>

    <lyrics>
        <chorus>
            <line>I don't know why this world keeps turning round and round</line>
            <line>But I wish it would stop and let me off right now</line>
            <line>I don't know why this world keeps turning round and round</line>
            <line>But I wish it would stop and let me off right now</line>
        </chorus>

        <verse>
            <line>Yes, man! As the world turns</line>
            <line>We all experience things in life</line>
            <line>Trials and tribulations that we all must go through</line>
            <line>When someone wants to test us</line>
            <line>When someone tries our patience</line>
        </verse>

        <verse>
            <line>I hang with a bunch of hippies and wacky tobacco planters</line>
            <line>Who swallow lit roaches and light up like jack-o-lanterns</line>
            <line>Outsidaz, baby, and we suin' the courts</line>
            <line>‘Cause we dope as <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase> and only get a 2 in The
                Source</line>
            <line>They never should've booted me outta reform school</line>
            <line>Deformed fool, taking a <phrase type="profanity">shit</phrase> in a warm
                pool</line>
            <line>'Til they threw me out the Ramada Inn</line>
            <line>I said it wasn't me, I got a twin</line>
            <line>(Oh my God, it's you! Not again!)</line>
            <line>It all started when my mother took my bike away</line>
            <line><phrase type="lifeEvent">‘Cause I murdered my guinea pig</phrase></line>
            <line>And stuck him in the microwave</line>
            <line>After that, it was straight to the 40 ouncers</line>
            <line>Slappin' teachers and jackin' off in front of my counselors</line>
            <line>Class clown freshman, dressed like Les Nessman</line>
            <line><phrase type="profanity">Fuck</phrase> the next lesson! I'll pass the test
                guessin'</line>
            <line>And all the other kids said: "Eminem is a thizz head</line>
            <line>He'll never last, the only class he'll ever pass is phys-ed."</line>
            <line>Maybe true, 'til I told this <phrase type="dt">bitch</phrase> in gym class</line>
            <line>That she was too fat to swim laps, she need a Slim Fast</line>
            <line>(Who? Me?) Yeah, <phrase type="dt">bitch</phrase>, you so big</line>
            <line>You walked into Vic Tanny's and stepped on Jenny Craig</line>
            <line>She picked me up to snap me like a skinny twig</line>
            <line>Put me in a headlock, then I thought of my guinea pig</line>
            <line>I felt the evilness and started transformin'</line>
            <line>It began stormin', I heard a bunch of cheering fans swarmin'</line>
            <line>Grabbed that <phrase type="dt">bitch</phrase> by her hair, drug her across the
                ground</line>
            <line>And took her up to the highest diving board</line>
            <line>And tossed her down</line>
            <line>Sorry coach, it's too late to tell me stop</line>
            <line>While I drop this <phrase type="dt">bitch</phrase> face down and watch her belly
                flop</line>
        </verse>

        <chorus>
            <line>I don't know why this world keeps turning round and round</line>
            <line>But I wish it would stop and let me off right now</line>
        </chorus>

        <verse>
            <line>As the world turns, these are the days of our lives</line>
            <line>These are the things that we must go through, day by day</line>
        </verse>

        <verse>
            <line>We drive around in million dollar sports cars</line>
            <line>While little kids hide this tape</line>
            <line>From their parents like bad report cards</line>
            <line>Outsidaz, and we suin' the courts</line>
            <line>‘Cause we dope as <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase> and only get a 2 in The
                Source</line>
            <line>Hypochondriac, hanging out at the laundromat</line>
            <line>Where all the raunchy, fat, white, <phrase type="dt">trashy blondes</phrase> be
                at</line>
            <line>Dressed like a sailor, standin' by a pail of garbage</line>
            <line>It's almost dark and I'm still tryna nail a <phrase type="dt">trailer park
                    bitch</phrase></line>
            <line>I met a slut and said: "What up? It's nice to meet ya</line>
            <line>I'd like to treat you to a Faygo and a slice of pizza</line>
            <line>But I'm broke as <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase></line>
            <line>And I don't get paid 'til the first of next month</line>
            <line>But if you would care to join me</line>
            <line>I was about to roll this next blunt</line>
            <line>But I ain't got no weed, no Phillies or no papers</line>
            <line>Plus I'm a rapist and a repeated prison escapist</line>
            <line>So give me all your money</line>
            <line>And don't try nothing funny, ‘cause you know your stinking <phrase
                    type="profanity">ass</phrase> is too fat to try to outrun me."</line>
            <line>I went to grab my gun, that's when her <phrase type="profanity">ass</phrase> put
                it on me</line>
            <line>With an uppercut and hit me with a basket of laundry</line>
            <line>I fell through the glass doors, started causing a scene</line>
            <line>Slid across the floor and flew right into a washing machine</line>
            <line>Jumped up with a broken back</line>
            <line>Thank God I was smokin' crack</line>
            <line>All day, and doped up on coke and smack</line>
            <line>All I wanted to do was rape the <phrase type="profanity">bitch</phrase> and snatch
                her purse</line>
            <line>Now I wanna kill her, but yo, I gotta catch her first</line>
            <line>Ran through Rally's parking lot and took a shortcut</line>
            <line>Saw the house she ran up in and shot her <phrase type="profanity">fuckin'</phrase>
                porch up</line>
            <line>Kicked the door down to murder this divorced <phrase type="dt"
                >slut</phrase></line>
            <line>Looked around the room</line>
            <line>That's when I seen her bedroom door shut</line>
            <line>I know you're in there, <phrase type="dt">bitch</phrase>, I got my gun
                cocked</line>
            <line>You might as well come out now</line>
            <line>She said: "Come in! It's unlocked."</line>
            <line>I walked in and all I smelled was Liz Claiborne</line>
            <line>And seen her spread across the bed naked watchin' gay porn</line>
            <line>She said: "Come here, big boy! Let's get acquainted!"</line>
            <line>I turned around to run, twisted my ankle and sprained it</line>
            <line>She came at me at full speed, nothin' could stop her</line>
            <line>I shot her five times and every bullet bounced off her</line>
            <line>I started to beg: "No, please let go!"</line>
            <line>But she swallowed my <phrase type="profanity">fuckin'</phrase> leg whole like an
                egg roll</line>
            <line>With one leg left, now I'm hoppin' around crippled</line>
            <line>I grabbed my pocket knife and sliced off her right nipple</line>
            <line>Just tryna buy me some time</line>
            <line>Then I remembered this magic trick</line>
            <line>Duh-dah-duh-dah-duh-duh, go-go gadget dick!</line>
            <line>Whipped that <phrase type="profanity">shit</phrase> out, and ain't no doubt about
                it</line>
            <line>It hit the ground, caused an earthquake and power outage</line>
            <line>I shouted: "Now, <phrase type="dt">bitch</phrase>, let's see who gets the
                best!"</line>
            <line>Stuffed that <phrase type="profanity">shit</phrase> in crooked and <phrase
                    type="profanity">fucked</phrase> that fat <phrase type="dt">slut</phrase> to
                death</line>
            <line>(Come here, <phrase type="dt">bitch</phrase>, come here!</line>
            <line>Take this <phrase type="profanity">mothafuckin'</phrase> dick, <phrase type="dt"
                    >bitch</phrase>, come here!)</line>
        </verse>

        <chorus>
            <line>I don't know why this world keeps turning round and round</line>
            <line>But I wish it would stop and let me off right now</line>
            <line>I don't know why this world keeps turning round and round</line>
            <line>But I wish it would stop and let me off right now</line>
            <line>I don't know why this world keeps turning round and round</line>
            <line>But I wish it would stop and let me off right now</line>
        </chorus>

        <verse>
            <line>And as we go along, throughout the days of our lives</line>
            <line>We all face small obstacles and challenges everyday</line>
            <line>That we must go through, these are the things</line>
            <line>That surround us through our atmosphere, every day</line>
            <line>Every single day the world keeps turning</line>
        </verse>
    </lyrics>
</song>
