<song><head><songTitle><line>Bad Meets Evil</line></songTitle>
<artist><line>Eminem</line></artist>
<featuredArtist><line>Royce da 5’9”</line></featuredArtist>
<line>Eminem amd Bass Brothers</line>
<line>The Slim Shady EP</line>
<certification><line>Diamond</line></certification></head>

<lyrics><intro><line>[Intro: Cowboy (Jeff Bass)]</line>
<line>I reckon you ain't familiar with these here parts</line>
<line>You know, there's a story behind that there saloon</line>
<line>20 years ago, two outlaws took this whole town over</line>
<line>Sheriffs couldn't stop 'em</line>
<line>Quickest <phrase type="profanity">damn</phrase> gun-slingers I've ever seen</line>
<line>Got murdered in cold-blood</line>
<line>That old saloon there was their little 'home away from home'</line>
<line>They say the ghosts of Bad and Evil still live in that tavern</line>
<line>And on a quiet night, you can still hear</line>
<line>The footsteps of Slim Shady and Royce da 5'9"</line></intro>

<verse><line>[Verse 1: Eminem]</line>
<line>I don't speak, I float in the air, wrapped in a sheet</line>
<line>I'm not a real person, I'm a ghost trapped in a beat</line>
<line>I translate when my voice is read through a seismograph</line>
<line>And the noise is spread</line>
<line>Picked up and transmitted through Royce's head</line>
<line>Trap him in his room, possess him and hoist his bed</line>
<line>'Til the evilness flows through his blood like poisonous lead</line>
<line>Told him each one of his boys is dead</line>
<line>I asked him to come to the dark side</line>
<line>He made a choice and said...</line></verse>

<verse><line>[Verse 2: Royce da 5'9"]</line>
<line>Who hard? Yo, I done heard worse</line>
<line>We can get in two cars and accelerate at each other</line>
<line>To see which one'll swerve first</line>
<line>Two blind bandits panic whose mental capacity holds that of a globe on top of nine other planets</line>
<line>Kissed the cheek of the Devil</line>
<line>Intelligence level is hellier than treble peakin'</line>
<line>On speakers in the ghetto</line>
<line>Dismissal, I'm not a fair man</line>
<line>Disgraced the race of an atheist</line>
<line>Interceptin' missiles with my bare hands like a patriot</line>
<line>One track sliced without swords</line>
<line>I buried the Christ corpse, in my past life</line>
<line>When the black knight mounted the white horse</line>
<line>And stay over-worked</line>
<line>It's like the Nazis and the Nation</line>
<line>Collaboratin', attemptin' to take over the Earth</line></verse>

<chorus><line>[Hook 1: Eminem]</line>
<line>‘Cause this is what happens when Bad meets Evil</line>
<line>And we hit the trees 'til we look like Vietnamese people</line>
<line>He's Evil, and I'm Bad like Steve Seagal</line>
<line>Above the law ‘cause I don't agree with police either</line>
<line>(<phrase type="profanity">Shit</phrase>, me neither)</line></chorus>

<line>[Verse 3: Eminem]</line>
<line>We ain't eager to be legal</line>
<line>So please leave me with the keys to your Jeep Eagle</line>
<line>I breathe ether in three lethal amounts</line>
<line>While I stab myself in the knee with a diseased needle</line>
<line>Releasin' <phrase type="emotion">rage</phrase> on anybody in squeezin' range</line>
<line>Cold enough to make the seasons change into freezin' rain</line>
<line>(He's insane) No I'm not, I just want to shoot up</line>
<line>And I'm pissed off, ‘cause I can't find a decent vein</line>

<line>[Verse 4: Royce da 5'9"]</line>
<line>The disaster with dreads</line>
<line>I'm bad enough to commit suicide</line>
<line>And survive long enough to kill my soul after I'm dead</line>
<line>When in danger, it's funny</line>
<line>Actually my flavor's similar to a waiter</line>
<line>‘Cause I serve any stranger with money</line>
<line>I spray a hundred</line>
<line>Man, until they joint chains, while slippin' bullets at point-blank range like they was punches</line>
<line>Piss on a flag and burn it</line>
<line>Murder you then come to your funeral</line>
<line>Service lobby and strangle your body to confirm it</line>
<line>Whippin' human <phrase type="profanity">ass</phrase>, throwin' blows, crackin' jaws</line>
<line>With my fists wrapped in gauze, dipped in glue and glass</line>
<line>I'm blazin' emcees, at the same time amazin' emcees</line>
<line>Somehow, emcees ain't that eyebrow-raisin' to me</line>
<line>From all of angles of us, flash a MAC loud enough</line>
<line>To cast a avalanche and bust 'til volcanoes erupt</line>

<line>[Spoken: Eminem]</line>
<line>Hello? Ayo, what’s up?</line>
<line>We’re coming to get you!</line>
<line>Stop! THEY KNOW IT’S US!!!</line>

<verse><line>[Verse 5: Eminem]</line>
<line>I used to be a loudmouth, remember me?</line>
<line>I'm the one who burned your house down, well, I'm out now</line>
<line>And this time I'm comin' back to blow your house up</line>
<line>And I ain't gon' leave you a window to jump out of</line>
<line>Give me two fat tabs and three shrooms</line>
<line>And you won't see me, like fat people in steam rooms</line>
<line>And when I go to hell and I'm gettin' ready to leave</line>
<line>I'ma put air in a bag and charge people to breathe</line></verse>

<line>[Hook 2: Royce da 5'9"]</line>
<line>‘Cause this is what happens when Bad meets Evil</line>
<line>And we hit the trees 'til we look like Vietnamese people</line>
<line>He's Evil, and I'm Bad like Steve Seagal</line>
<line>Against peaceful, see you in Hell for the sequel</line>
<line>(We'll be waiting) See you in Hell</line>
<line>Wall Street, Royce Da 5'9", Slim Shady</line>
<line>See you in Hell for the sequel (bye-bye)</line>
<line>Bad Meets Evil, what ('til next time)</line>

<line>[Outro: Cowboy (Jeff Bass)]</line>
<line>And so that's the story when Bad meets Evil</line>
<line>Two of the most wanted individuals in the county</line>
<line>Made Jesse James and Billy the Kid</line>
<line>Look like law-abiding citizens</line>
<line>It's too bad they had to go out the way they did</line>
<line>Got shot in the back coming out of that old saloon</line>
<line>But their spirits still live on 'til this day</line>
<line>Shhh… wait, did y'all hear that?</line></lyrics>

</song>