<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song><head><songTitle>Heartz of Men</songTitle>
<singer>2Pac</singer>
<producers>2Pac and DJ Quik</producers>
<album>All Eyez on Me</album>
<certification>Diamond</certification></head>

<lyrics><intro>Hey, Suge, what I tell you, <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>?
<phrase type="lifeEvent">When I come out of jail, what I was gonna do?</phrase>
I was gonna start diggin' into these <phrase type="profanity">niggas'</phrase> chest, right?
Heh, watch this!
Hey, Quik, let me see them binoculars, <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>, the binoculars!
Hahahahaha! Yeah, <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>, time to ride!
Grab your bulletproof vest, <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>
'Cause it's gonna be a long one
Now, me and Quik finna show you <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> what it's like on this side—the real side
Now, on this ride there's gonna be some real <phrase type="profanity">motherfuckers</phrase>
And there's gonna be some <phrase type="dt">pussies</phrase>
Now, the real <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> gonna be the ones with money and bitches
The <phrase type="dt">pussies</phrase> gonna be the <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> on the floor bleedin'
Now, everybody keep your eyes on the prize
'Cause the ride get tricky
See, you got some <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> on your side that say they're your friends, but, in real life they your enemies
And then you got some <phrase type="profanity">motherfuckers</phrase> that say they your enemies
But in real life they eyes is on your money
See, the enemies will say they true
But in real life those <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> will be snitches
It's a dirty game, y'all
Y'all gotta be careful about who you <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase> with and who you don't <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase> with, 'cause the <phrase type="profanity">shit</phrase> get wild, y'all
Keep your mind on your riches, baby!
Keep your mind on your riches!</intro>

<verse>9-1-1, it's an emergency, cowards tried to murder me
From hood to the 'burbs, everyone of you <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> heard of me
Shit, I'm legendary, <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> scaried and paralyzed
Nothin' more I <phrase type="emotion">despise</phrase> than a liar, cowards die
My mama told me when I was a seed
Just a vicious <phrase type="profanity">motherfucker</phrase>, why these devils left me free?
I proceed to make 'em shiver when I deliver
Criminal lyrics from a worldwide mob figure
Thug <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> from everywhere, Mr. Makaveli
<phrase type="profanity">Niggas</phrase> is waitin' for some thug <phrase type="profanity">shit</phrase>, that's what they tell me
So many rumors, but I'm infinite, Immortal Outlaw
Switchin' up on you ordinary <phrase type="profanity">bitches</phrase> like a southpaw: you get left
And every breath I breathe until the moment I'm deceased
Will be another moment ballin' as a G
I rip the crowd, then I start again, eternally, I live in sin
Until the moment that they let me breathe again; the hearts of men</verse>

<chorus>The hearts of men</chorus>

    <verse>My lyrical verge with so much pain, to some <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> it hurts
My guns bust, if you ain't one of us it gets worse
<phrase type="profanity">Bitch</phrase> <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> get their eyes swoll in fly mode
I'm a homicidal outlaw, and five-o
Get your lights on, the fight's on
Tonight's gonna be a <phrase type="profanity">fuckin'</phrase> fight so we might roll
My own homies say I'm heartless
But I'm a G to this until the day I'm gone, that's regardless
Ride by, <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> bow down, thought I'd rot in jail
Paid bail, well, a <phrase type="profanity">nigga's</phrase> out now
Throw up your hands if you thugged out
First <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase> act up, first <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase> gettin' drugged out
I can be a villain if you let me
A <phrase type="profanity">motherfucker</phrase> if you do upset me
Tell the cops to come and get me
Rip the crowd like a phone number, then start again
Don't have no <phrase type="profanity">motherfuckin'</phrase> friends
<phrase type="profanity">Nigga</phrase>, look inside the hearts of men
</verse>
<chorus>
In the hearts of men</chorus>

<verse>To all my <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> engaged in makin' money in the fifty states
Keep your mind on your chips and <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase> a <phrase type="dt">punk bitch</phrase>
No longer livin' in <phrase type="emotion">fear</phrase>, my pistol close in hand
Convinced that this is my year like I'm the chosen man
Give me my money and label me as a don
If <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> is havin' problems, smoke 'em, fire and bomb
I died and came back, I hustle with these lyrics
As if it's a game of crack, thuggin' is in my spirit
I'm lost and not knowin'
Scarred up but still flowin', energized and still goin'
Uhh, can it be fate, that makes a sick <phrase type="profanity">motherfucker</phrase> break
On these <phrase type="profanity">jealous-ass</phrase> cowards 'cause they evil and fake?
What will it take? Give me that bass line, I'm feelin' bomb
Death Row, baby, don't be alarmed
The homie Quik gave a <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase> a beat and let me start again
Represent, 'cause I've been sent, the hearts of men</verse></lyrics>
</song>