<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../rapSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <head>
        <songTitle>I'm Shady</songTitle>
        <artist>Eminem</artist>
        <producer>Eminem</producer>
        <producer>Bass Brothers</producer>
        <album>The Slim Shady EP</album>
        <certification>Diamond</certification>
    </head>

    <lyrics>
        <verse>
            <line>Who came through with two Glocks to terrorize your borough? (Huh?!)</line>
            <line>Told you how to slap dips and murder your girl? (I did)</line>
            <line>Gave you all the finger and told you to sit and twirl</line>
            <line>Sold a billion tapes, and still screamed "<phrase type="profanity">Fuck</phrase>
                the world!"</line>
            <line>(Slim Shady…) so come and kill me while my name's hot</line>
            <line>And shoot me 25 times in the same spot</line>
            <line>I think I got a generation brainwashed</line>
            <line>To pop pills and smoke pot 'til they brains rot</line>
            <line>Stop they blood flow until they veins clot</line>
            <line>I need a pain shot and a shot of plain Scotch</line>
            <line>Purple haze and acid raindrops</line>
            <line>Spike the punch at the party and drink pop</line>
            <line>Shaved my armpits and wore a tank top</line>
            <line>Bad Boy, I told you that I can't stop</line>
            <line>You gotta make 'em <phrase type="emotion">fear</phrase> you before you make 'em
                feel you</line>
            <line>So everybody buy my <phrase type="profanity">shit</phrase> or I'ma come and kill
                you</line>
        </verse>

        <chorus>
            <line>I got mushrooms, I got acid</line>
            <line>I got tabs and aspirin tablets</line>
            <line>I'm your brother when you need</line>
            <line>Some good weed to set you free</line>
            <line>You know me, I'm your friend</line>
            <line>When you need a Mini Thin</line>
            <line>(I'm Slim Shady…) I'm Shady!</line>
        </chorus>

        <verse>
            <line>I like happy things, I'm really calm and peaceful</line>
            <line>I like birds, bees, I like people</line>
            <line>I like funny things that make me happy and gleeful</line>
            <line>Like when my teacher sucked my wee-wee in preschool</line>
            <line>The ill type, I stab myself with a steel spike</line>
            <line>While I blow my brain out just to see what it feels like</line>
            <line>‘Cause this is how I am in real life</line>
            <line>I don't want to just die a normal death</line>
            <line>I wanna be killed twice</line>
            <line>How you gonna scare somebody with a gun threat</line>
            <line>When they high off of drugs they haven't even done yet?</line>
            <line>So bring the money by tonight, ‘cause your wife</line>
            <line>Said this the biggest knife she ever saw in her life (help me!)</line>
            <line>I try to keep it positive and play it cool</line>
            <line>Shoot up the playground and tell the kids to stay in school ("Stay in
                school!")</line>
            <line>‘Cause I'm the one they can relate to and look up to better</line>
            <line>Tonight I think I'll write my biggest fan a <phrase type="profanity"
                    >fuck-you</phrase> letter</line>
        </verse>

        <chorus>
            <line>I got mushrooms, I got acid</line>
            <line>I got tabs and aspirin tablets</line>
            <line>I'm your brother when you need</line>
            <line>Some good weed to set you free</line>
            <line>You know me, I'm your friend</line>
            <line>When you need a Mini Thin</line>
            <line>(I'm Slim Shady…) I'm Shady!</line>
        </chorus>

        <verse>
            <line>I listen to your demo tape</line>
            <line>And act like I don't like it ("Ahh, that <phrase type="profanity">shit</phrase> is
                wack!")</line>
            <line>Six months later you hear your lyrics on my <phrase type="profanity"
                >shit</phrase></line>
            <line>("That's my <phrase type="profanity">shit</phrase>!")</line>
            <line>People don't buy <phrase type="profanity">shit</phrase> no more, they just dub
                it</line>
            <line>That's why I'm still broke and had the number-one club hit</line>
            <line>But they love it when you make your business public</line>
            <line>So <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase> it, I've got herpes while we on the
                subject (uh-huh)</line>
            <line>And if I told you I had AIDS, y'all would play it</line>
            <line>‘Cause you stupid <phrase type="profanity">mothafuckas</phrase> think I'm playin'
                when I say it</line>
            <line>Well, I do take pills, don't do speed</line>
            <line>Don't do crack, don't do coke, I do smoke weed</line>
            <line>Don't do smack, I do do shrooms, do drink beer</line>
            <line>I just wanna make a few things clear</line>
            <line>My baby mama's not dead, she's still alive and <phrase type="profanity"
                    >bitchin'</phrase></line>
            <line>And I don't have herpes, my dick's just itchin'</line>
            <line>It's not syphilis, and as for being AIDS-infested</line>
            <line>I don't know yet, I'm too scared to get tested</line>
        </verse>

        <chorus>
            <line>I got mushrooms, I got acid</line>
            <line>I got tabs and aspirin tablets</line>
            <line>I'm your brother when you need</line>
            <line>Some good weed to set you free</line>
            <line>You know me, I'm your friend</line>
            <line>When you need a Mini Thin</line>
            <line>(I'm Slim Shady…) I'm Shady!</line>
        </chorus>

        <outro>
            <line>Told you I was Shady</line>
            <line>Y'all didn't believe me</line>
            <line>I'm Shady!</line>
            <line>And that's my name</line>
        </outro>
    </lyrics>
</song>
