<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song><head><songTitle>No More Pain</songTitle>
<singer>2Pac</singer>
<producers>Timbaland and DeVante Swing</producers>
<album>All Eyez on Me</album>
<certification>Diamond</certification></head>

<lyrics><intro>Hey DeVante
<phrase type="profanity">Nigga</phrase>, don'tcha know we're gonna sow up every <phrase type="profanity">bitch</phrase> in the country
Me and you, up in the same <phrase type="profanity">motherfuckin'</phrase> room
On the same level
This <phrase type="profanity">shit</phrase> here, hahahaha
Please, no more pain
That's right <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>
Hey drop that <phrase type="profanity">shit</phrase> boy</intro>

<verse>My adversaries cry like <phrase type="dt">hoes</phrase> fully eradicate my foes
My lyrics explode on contact, gamin' you <phrase type="dt">hoes</phrase>
Who else but Mama's only son, <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase> the phony <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> I'm the one
Say my name, watch <phrase type="profanity">bitches</phrase> come
Now fire when ready, stay watchin' our figure
Increase speed, make you <phrase type="profanity">motherfuckers</phrase> bleed from your mouth quicker
Plus all these <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> that you run with, be on some dumb <phrase type="profanity">shit</phrase>
Trickin' on <phrase type="dt">hoes</phrase>, I ain't the one <phrase type="profanity">bitch</phrase>
Holla my name and witness game official, it's so sick
Have every single <phrase type="profanity">bitch</phrase> that came witchu, on my dick
Plus this alcohol increases the chance to be deceased
I'm movin' you stupid <phrase type="profanity">bitches</phrase>, vicious telekinesis
Am I reachin' your brain? <phrase type="profanity">Nigga</phrase> how can I explain?
How vicious this Thug <phrase type="profanity">motherfucker</phrase> came
When I die, I want to be a living legend, say my name
Affiliated with this <phrase type="profanity">motherfuckin'</phrase> game, with no more pain</verse>

<chorus>I came to bring the pain, hardcore to the brain
Let's go inside my astral plane (no more pain)
I came to bring the pain, hardcore to the brain
Let's go inside my astral plane (no more pain)
I came to bring the pain, hardcore to the brain
Let's go inside my astral plane (no more pain)
I came to bring the pain, hardcore to the brain
Let's go inside my astral plane (no more pain)</chorus>

<verse>Line up my adversaries, blast on sight
And <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase> your boyfriend <phrase type="profanity">bitch</phrase>, I want some <phrase type="profanity">ass</phrase> tonight You know my steelo, Alize and Cristal, weed
Sure you heard of all the freaky <phrase type="profanity">shit</phrase> they say about me, huh
Plus all you busters is <phrase type="emotion">jealous</phrase>, pull your gun out and blast
I dare you <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> to open fire, I'll murder that <phrase type="profanity">ass</phrase>
And disappear before the, cops come runnin'
My Glock's spittin' rounds, <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> fallin' down clutchin' they stomach
It's Westside, Death Row, Thug <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> on the rise
Busters shot me five times, real <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> don't die
Can ya hear me?, laced with this game, I know you fear me
Spit the secret to war, so cowards fear me
My only <phrase type="emotion">fear</phrase> of death is reincarnation
Heart of a solider with a brain to teach your whole nation
And feelin' no more pain</verse>

<chorus>I came to bring the pain, hardcore to the brain
Let's go inside my astral plane (no more pain)
I came to bring the pain, hardcore to the brain
Let's go inside my astral plane (yeah <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>, no more pain)
I came to bring the pain, hardcore to the brain (what, what <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>)
Let's go inside my astral plane (no more pain)
I came to bring the pain, hardcore to the brain
Let's go inside my astral plane (no more pain)
I came to bring the pain, hardcore to the brain (no pain <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>)
Let's go inside my astral plane (no pain)</chorus>

<verse>Bury me that's what they all say
It's time to make a killin', sure to make a million with DeVante
<phrase type="profanity">Bitch</phrase> I know you want me, what your mouth say?, now, watch your eyes
You don't wanna get with me, that's a lie
I got my hands on your hips, no time to <phrase type="profanity">bullshit</phrase>
Freaky <phrase type="profanity">bitch</phrase>, come give me kiss
Tell them <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> from other areas, brothers from here
So obsessed with this money makin' it ain't nothin' we <phrase type="emotion">fear</phrase>
Now they label me a troublemaker, cause I'm a ridah
Death to you playa haters, don't let me find ya
Mama made me rugged, Baptize the public
Now you all thugs, <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase> don't you love it
It's similar to multiple gunshots, retaliation is a must
Wasn't too sure what you facin' so watch the guns bust
You <phrase type="profanity">niggas'll</phrase> bleed, <phrase type="profanity">fuckin'</phrase> with me you'll be deceased
Never restin' in peace, <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>
With no more pain</verse>

<chorus>I came to bring the pain, hardcore to the brain
Let's go inside my astral plane
I came to bring the pain, hardcore to the brain
Let's go inside my astral plane</chorus>

<verse>Hahahahaha, yeah <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>, yeah! Hahahaha
No more pain
It's just like that <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>, like that yeah
No more pain
<phrase type="profanity">Motherfuckers</phrase> can't handle that shit
Much too much for these <phrase type="profanity">bitches</phrase>
No more pain
Feel me <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>? Feel me?
How you figure you can <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase> with me?
Fully automatic type <phrase type="profanity">shit</phrase>
No more pain
Coward <phrase type="profanity">ass</phrase> <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase>, cowards
Come put your mouth on this pistol <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>
Come put your mouth on the pistol, no more pain
Close your eyes <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>, do it
Die in the dark, no more pain
Death Row, so what you <phrase type="profanity">motherfuckers</phrase> do?
Hey that's DeVante droppin' that beat like that BEYATCH
In case you wonderin'
And <phrase type="emotion">jealous</phrase> <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase>, hahaha, see y'all <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase>
    <phrase type="profanity">Motherfuckin'</phrase> <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> are <phrase type="profanity">shit</phrase>
Hey
Westsiiiiiide! Death to everybody that ain't down with me
That's on, feel me? Hahaha
Oh yeah, to the cowards, you know who you are, it's still Bad Boy Killa
Just feel that, Thug Life, <phrase type="profanity">shit</phrase> don't stop
Fat <phrase type="profanity">motherfuckers</phrase> got Downs Syndrome, <phrase type="profanity">motherfuckers</phrase>
Weak <phrase type="profanity">ass</phrase> <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase>, dancers turned <phrase type="profanity">fuckin'</phrase> CEOs
Put your mouth on this pistol <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>
Put your mouth on the pistol!
Hahahaha, yeah <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase> no more pain
Prison ain't changed me <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>, it made me worse
Feel me <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>, haha
No more pain
Hey DeVante I'm givin' these <phrase type="profanity">motherfuckers</phrase> choices
<phrase type="profanity">Niggas</phrase> can roll with us, or they can be rolled up under us
That's on you <phrase type="profanity">nigga</phrase>, what you wanna do?
Last year we was lettin' these <phrase type="profanity">niggas</phrase> kick up dust
This year you <phrase type="profanity">motherfuckers</phrase> gonna be dust</verse></lyrics></song>
