<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../rapSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <head>
        <songTitle>Role Model</songTitle>
        <artist>Eminem</artist>
        <producer>Dr. Dre</producer>
        <producer>Mel-Man</producer>
        <album>The Slim Shady EP</album>
        <certification>Diamond</certification>
        <order>35</order>
    </head>

    <lyrics>
        <intro>
            <line>Okay, I'm going to attempt to drown myself</line>
            <line>You can try this at home</line>
            <line>You can be just like me</line>
            <line>Mic check, one-two, we recording?</line>
        </intro>

        <verse>
            <line>I'm cancerous</line>
            <line>So when I diss, you wouldn't wanna answer this</line>
            <line>If you responded back with a battle rap you wrote for Canibus</line>
            <line>I'll strangle you to death, then I'll choke you again</line>
            <line>And break your <phrase type="profanity">fucking</phrase> legs 'til your bones poke
                through your skin</line>
            <line>You beef with me, I'ma even the score equally</line>
            <line>Take you on Jerry Springer and beat your <phrase type="profanity">ass</phrase>
                legally</line>
            <line>I get too blunted off of funny home grown</line>
            <line>‘Cause when I smoke out I hit the trees harder than Sonny Bono</line>
            <line>(Oh no!) So if I said I never did drugs</line>
            <line>That would mean I lie and get <phrase type="profanity">fucked</phrase></line>
            <line>More than the President does</line>
            <line>Hilary Clinton tried to slap me and call me a pervert</line>
            <line>I ripped her <phrase type="profanity">fucking</phrase> tonsils out and fed her
                sherbet (<phrase type="dt">Bitch</phrase>)</line>
            <line>My nerves hurt, and lately I'm on edge</line>
            <line>Grabbed Vanilla Ice and ripped out his blond dreads</line>
            <line>Every girl I ever went out with has gone les</line>
            <line>Follow me and do exactly what the song says</line>
            <line>Smoke weed, take pills, drop out of school, kill people</line>
            <line>And drink, jump behind the wheel like it was still legal</line>
            <line>I'm dumb enough to walk in a store and steal</line>
            <line>So I'm dumb enough to ask for a date with Lauryn Hill</line>
            <line>Some people only see that I'm white, ignorin' skill</line>
            <line>‘Cause I stand out like a green hat with a orange bill</line>
            <line>But I don't get pissed, y'all don't even see through the mist</line>
            <line>How the <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase> can I be white? I don't even
                exist</line>
            <line>I get a clean shave, bathe, go to a rave</line>
            <line>Die from an overdose and dig myself up out of my grave</line>
            <line>My middle finger won't go down, how do I wave?</line>
            <line>And this is how I'm supposed to teach kids how to behave?</line>
        </verse>

        <chorus>
            <line>Now follow me and do exactly what you see</line>
            <line>Don't you wanna grow up to be just like me?</line>
            <line>I slap women and eat shrooms then OD</line>
            <line>Now don't you want to grow up to be just like me?</line>
        </chorus>

        <verse>
            <line>Me and Marcus Allen went over to see Nicole</line>
            <line>When we heard a knock at the door, must've been Ron Gold</line>
            <line>Jumped behind the door, put the orgy on hold</line>
            <line>Killed them both, then smeared blood on the white Bronco</line>
            <line>(We did it!) My mind won't work if my spine don't jerk</line>
            <line>I slapped Garth Brooks out of his rhinestone shirt</line>
            <line>I'm not a player, just a ill rhyme sayer</line>
            <line>That'll spray a aerosol can up at the ozone layer</line>
            <line>My rap style's warped, I'm running out the morgue</line>
            <line>With your dead grandmother's corpse to throw it on your porch</line>
            <line>Jumped in a Chickenhawk cartoon with a cape on</line>
            <line>And beat up Foghorn Leghorn with an acorn</line>
            <line>I'm 'bout as normal as Norman Bates with deformative traits</line>
            <line>A premature birth that was four minutes late</line>
            <line>Mother, are you there? I love you</line>
            <line>I never meant to hit you over the head with that shovel</line>
            <line>Will someone please explain to my brain</line>
            <line>That I just severed the main vein with a chainsaw and I'm in pain?</line>
            <line>I take a breather and sigh; either I'm high</line>
            <line>Or I'm nuts, ‘cause if you ain't tilting this room, neither am I</line>
            <line>So when you see your mom with a thermometer</line>
            <line>Shoved in her <phrase type="profanity">ass</phrase>, then it probably is obvious I
                got it on with her</line>
            <line>‘Cause when I drop this solo <phrase type="profanity">shit</phrase>, it's over
                with</line>
            <line>I bought Cage's tape, opened it, and dubbed over it</line>
        </verse>

        <chorus>
            <line>I came to the club drunk with a fake ID</line>
            <line>Don't you wanna grow up to be just like me?</line>
            <line>I've been with ten women who got HIV</line>
            <line>Now don't you wanna grow up to be just like me?</line>
            <line>I got genital warts and it burns when I pee</line>
            <line>Don't you wanna grow up to be just like me?</line>
            <line>I tie a rope around my penis and jump from a tree</line>
            <line>You probably wanna grow up to be just like me</line>
        </chorus>
    </lyrics>
</song>
