<song><head><songTitle><line>Still Don't Give a Fuck</line></songTitle>
<artist><line>Eminem</line></artist>
<producer><line>Eminem and Bass Brothers</line></producer>
<album><line>The Slim Shady LP</line></album>
<certification><line>Diamond</line></certification></head>

<intro><line>A lot of people ask me, am I <phrase type="emotion">afraid</phrase> of death?</line>
<line><phrase type="profanity">Hell</phrase> yeah, I'm <phrase type="emotion">afraid</phrase> of death</line>
<line>I don't want to die yet</line>
<line>A lot of people think that I worship the devil</line>
<line>That I do all types of retarded <phrase type="profanity">shit</phrase></line>
<line>Look, I can't change the way I think</line>
<line>And I can't change the way I am</line>
<line>But if I offended you, good!</line>
<line>‘Cause I still don't give a <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase></line></intro>

<verse><line>I'm zonin' off of one joint, stoppin' a limo</line>
<line>Hopped in the window, shoppin' a demo at gunpoint</line>
<line>A lyricist without a clue, what year is this?</line>
<line><phrase type="profanity">Fuck</phrase> a needle, here's a sword, body pierce with this!</line>
<line>Livin' amok, never givin' a <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase></line>
<line>Give me the keys, I'm drunk, and I've never driven a truck</line>
<line>But I smoke dope in a cab</line>
<line>I'll stab you with the sharpest knife I can grab</line>
<line>Come back the next week and re-open your scab</line>
<line>A killer instinct runs in the blood</line>
<line>Emptyin' full clips and buryin' guns in the mud</line>
<line>I've calmed down now, I was heavy once into drugs</line>
<line>I could walk around straight for two months with a buzz</line>
<line>My brain's gone, my soul's worn, and my spirit is torn</line>
<line>The rest of my body's still bein' operated on</line>
<line>I'm ducked the <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase> down while I'm writin' this rhyme</line>
<line>‘Cause I'm probably gonna get struck with lightnin' this time</line></verse>

<line>[Hook]</line>
<line>For all the weed that I've smoked – yo, this blunt's for you</line>
<line>To all the people I've offended – yeah, <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase> you too!</line>
<line>To all the friends I used to have – yo, I miss my past</line>
<line>But the rest of you <phrase type="profanity">assholes</phrase> can kiss my <phrase type="profanity">ass</phrase></line>
<line>For all the drugs that I've done – yo, I'm still gonna do</line>
<line>To all the people I've offended – yeah, <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase> you too!</line>
<line>For every time I reminisce – yo, I miss my past</line>
<line>But I still don't give a <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase>, y'all can kiss my <phrase type="profanity">ass</phrase></line>

<verse><line>I walked into a gunfight with a knife to kill you</line>
<line>And cut you so fast, when your blood spilled it was still blue</line>
<line>I'll hang you till you dangle and chain you with both ankles</line>
<line>And pull you apart from both angles</line>
<line>I wanna crush your skull 'til your brains leaks out of your veins and bust open like broken water mains</line>
<line>So tell Saddam not to bother with makin' another bomb</line>
<line>‘Cause I'm crushin' the whole world in my palm</line>
<line>Got your girl on my arm, and I'm armed with a firearm</line>
<line>So big my entire arm is a giant firebomb</line>
<line>Buy your mom a shirt with a Slim Shady iron-on</line>
<line>And the pants to match ("Here, Momma, try 'em on!")</line>
<line>I get imaginative with a mouth full of adjectives</line>
<line>A brain full of adverbs, and a box full of laxatives</line>
<line>(<phrase type="profanity">Shittin'</phrase> on rappers) Causing hospital accidents</line>
<line>God, help me, before I commit some irresponsible acts again</line></verse>

<line>[Hook]</line>
<line>For all the weed that I've smoked – yo, this blunt's for you</line>
<line>To all the people I've offended – yeah, <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase> you too!</line>
<line>To all the friends I used to have – yo, I miss my past</line>
<line>But the rest of you <phrase type="profanity">assholes</phrase> can kiss my <phrase type="profanity">ass</phrase></line>
<line>For all the drugs that I've done – yo, I'm still gonna do</line>
<line>To all the people I've offended – yeah, <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase> you too!</line>
<line>For every time I reminisce – yo, I miss my past</line>
<line>But I still don't give a <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase>, y'all can kiss my <phrase type="profanity">ass</phrase></line>

<verse><line>I wanted an album so rugged nobody could touch it</line>
<lifeEvent><line>Spent a million a track and went over my budget</line></lifeEvent>
<line>Now how in the <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase> am I supposed to get out of debt?</line>
<line>I can't rap anymore, I just murdered the alphabet</line>
<line>Drug sickness got me doin' some bugged twitches</line>
<line>I'm withdrawin' from crack so bad my blood itches</line>
<line>I don't rap to get the women—<phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase> <phrase type="dt">bitches</phrase>!</line>
<line>Give me a fat <phrase type="dt">slut</phrase> that cooks and does dishes</line>
<line>Never ran with a clique, I'm a posse</line>
<line>Kamikaze, strappin' a <phrase type="profanity">motherfuckin'</phrase> bomb across me</line>
<line>From the second I was born my momma lost me</line>
<line>I'm a cross between Manson, Esham and Ozzy</line>
<line>I don't know why the <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase> I'm here in the first place</line>
<line>My worst day on this earth was my first birthday</line>
<line>Retarded? What did that nurse say?</line>
<line>Brain damage? <phrase type="profanity">Fuck</phrase>! I was born during an earthquake</line></verse>

<line>[Hook]</line>
<line>For all the weed that I've smoked – yo, this blunt's for you</line>
<line>To all the people I've offended – yeah, <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase> you too!</line>
<line>To all the friends I used to have – yo, I miss my past</line>
<line>But the rest of you <phrase type="profanity">assholes</phrase> can kiss my <phrase type="profanity">ass</phrase></line>
<line>For all the drugs that I've done – yo, I'm still gonna do</line>
<line>To all the people I've offended – yeah, <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase> you too!</line>
<line>For every time I reminisce – yo, I miss my past</line>
<line>But I still don't give a <phrase type="profanity">fuck</phrase>, y'all can kiss my <phrase type="profanity">ass</phrase></line>

</song>